megagoods.com 2005-03-05

# MegaGoods.com Wholesale Consumer Electronics DropShipper.

**MegaGoods.com Privacy Policy**  
  
---  
  
**_MegaGoods.com_** believes that the establishment of trust and privacy is instrumental to the continued growth of the Internet. We at **_MegaGoods.com_** have created this privacy statement to demonstrate our corporate commitment to individual privacy. The policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services. By using **_MegaGoods.com_** web site, you agree to the terms and conditions set forth below.  
  
**Collection of Personal Information**  
  
**_MegaGoods.com_** collects personal information including, without limitations, name, address, e-mail address, telephone, demographic data and member identification number from its members and users. **_MegaGoods.com_** may collect such personal information as part of the registration process for members or when members or users submit comments or other correspondence to **_MegaGoods.com_** through its web site or otherwise. Additionally, **_MegaGoods.com_** may collect personal information through its web site by using cookies or other methods of monitoring web usage. We do not market, sell, or trade this information to any outside companies, but collected information may be shared with our business partners. We may, at times, use the demographic information as a marketing or promotional tool. When we do that, we will make sure it remains entirely anonymous.  
  
**Cookies**  
  
**_MegaGoods.com_** uses cookies to keep track of its members' and users' activity.  The type of cookies we use do not get stored on your computer, rather they expire once the browser is closed.  
  
**Security**  
  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (a valid email address), unique identifiers (a password), financial information (credit card number), and demographic information (such as a zip code).  When this type of information is collected it travels through the Internet in encrypted form. ** _MegaGoods.com_** uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which provides strong cryptography, to transfer all of the personal information to **_MegaGoods.com_**.  Financial and login information (password) are encrypted and stored in that form on **_MegaGoods.com_** servers.  
  
If you have questions concerning this policy please email us at [privacy@megagoods.com](mailto:privacy@megagoods.com)
